<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<metadata
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/">
<dc:title>A bittersweet goodbye</dc:title>
<dc:creator>Nicole Marenghi </dc:creator>
<dc:subject class="BT">Pain </dc:subject>
<dc:subject class="NT">Travelling</dc:subject>
<dc:subject class="NT">Study abroad</dc:subject>
<dcterms:abstract> This is a story written by Nicole Marenghi about her Erasmus experience, interrupted for Covid-19 pandemy. </dcterms:abstract>
<dc:description>E poi succede. Ti svegli la mattina, ti arriva una chiamata: alle 6 del mattino seguente parte l’ultimo volo che può riportarti in Italia. Così devi decidere e hai poco tempo. Vai? Metti fine al tuo Erasmus? Ma qui si sta ancora bene, è meglio che in Italia, ci dicono. O rimani? Ma se il virus si espande? Hai la consapevolezza che se qui il virus si dovesse scatenare come in Italia, sicuramente non avrebbero le strutture per affrontare tale situazione. Così decidi: domani si torna. E inizi a rimettere via tutto in valigia, speranza, amarezza, rabbia e paura. Neanche il tempo di comprare una calamita per il frigo. Ma per mettere su una pasta e riempirti la pancia di матцун e lavash il tempo c'è. E ti prepari a lasciare quello che stavi costruendo, dopo solo un mese. Disdici la casa, contatti l'università e rinunci ai piani che ti eri fatta. Rinunci un po' alla libertà. Però, Armenia, io spero di tornare.</dc:description>
<dc:description>It happens. You wake up in the morning and you receive a call: next morning at 6 AM the last flight to Italy leaves. So you have to decide, you have short time available. Leaving? Ending your Erasmus? But the situation here it’s better than in Italy, they say. Or staying? And what if the virus spreads? You are conscious that if the virus would spread here as in Italy, they didn’t have appropriate tools to face this situation. So you decide: tomorrow you’ll leave. So you start packing your bags and you put there everything: hope, bitterness,  fear and anger. You don’t even have the time to buy a magnet for the fridge! But you have the time to cook  pasta and eat матцун and lavash. So you prepare yourself to leave what you were building, after only one month. Call of the house, contact university and give up on plans you made. Give up on a bit of freedom. But, Armenia, I hope to come back to you.</dc:description>
<dc:publisher>IMOW - In My Own Words</dc:publisher>
<dc:publisher>Github</dc:publisher>
<dc:date xsi:type="dcterms:W3CDTF">unknown</dc:date>
<dc:type>Video </dc:type>
<dc:format>mp4</dc:format>
<dc:source>User Provided</dc:source>
<dc:language>It</dc:language>
<dc:language>En</dc:language>
<dcterms:isPartOf>Pain</dcterms:isPartOf>
<dc:rights> Every right issues about the website and its content are specified in the Privacy Policy dedicated page that you can consult here </dc:rights>
<dcterms:rightsholder>Every right issues about the website and its content are specified in the Privacy Policy dedicated page that you can consult here </dcterms:rightsholder>

</metadata>