<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<metadata
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/">
<dc:title>Metamorfosi</dc:title>
<dc:creator>Andrea Cocca</dc:creator>
<dc:subject class="BT">Celebrations</dc:subject>
<dc:subject class="NT">Birth</dc:subject>
<dc:subject class="NT">Nature</dc:subject>
<dcterms:abstract>This is a photograph taken by Andrea Cocca during quarantine.</dcterms:abstract>
<dc:description>Ho scattato questa foto nel giardino di casa, a inizio maggio.
É una di quelle immagini delle quali, probabilmente, non mi sarei accorto, senza lockdown. Questo periodo di fermo forzato ha indubbiamente influito sul modo in cui recepiamo ciò che ci circonda, rallentando a dismisura ritmi quotidiani che, altrimenti, avrebbero portato via con sé nella loro frenesia anche attimi o dettagli particolari, come questo bruco, in gita su una foglia, nel mio giardino, illuminato da un fascio di luce.
Penso che sia questo uno dei lati più positivi della situazione vissuta, la decompressione dalle forzature di una vita produttiva per riposizionarci nel mondo come esseri viventi in relazione a un contesto naturale al quale apparteniamo.
E dalla natura si può prendere spunto e immaginare che questo lockdown sia stato come un bozzolo nel quale un altro tipo di bruco si rinchiude, prima di tramutarsi in farfalla. 
</dc:description>
<dc:description>I took this picture in my house garden, in May. 
It is one of those images that, probably, I would have never payed attention to, without lockdown. This period of quarantine has definitely influenced our way of looking at what surround us, letting up our routine that in ordinary days would have taken away particular details like this caterpillar on a leaf, in my garden, illuminated by ray of light. 
I think that this is one of the bright side of the situation we’ve experienced: a life that slows down to reborn as human beings that draw a relationship between themselves and nature around. 
By nature we can be inspired and imagine that this lockdown has been like a cocoon where a caterpillar grows, before turning into a beautiful butterfly.
</dc:description>
<dc:publisher>IMOW - In My Own Words</dc:publisher>
<dc:publisher>Github</dc:publisher>
<dc:date xsi:type="dcterms:W3CDTF">08-05-2020</dc:date>
<dc:type>Image</dc:type>
<dc:format>jpg</dc:format>
<dc:source>User Provided</dc:source>
<dc:language>It</dc:language>
<dc:language>En</dc:language>
<dcterms:isPartOf>Celebrations</dcterms:isPartOf>
<dc:rights>Every right issues about the website and its content are specified in the Privacy Policy dedicated page that you can consult here: https://imowvirtualmuseum.github.io/GDPR_IMOW.pdf</dc:rights>
<dcterms:rightsholder>Every right issues about the website and its content are specified in the Privacy Policy dedicated page that you can consult here: https://imowvirtualmuseum.github.io/GDPR_IMOW.pdf</dcterms:rightsholder>

</metadata>