<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<metadata
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/">
<dc:title>Ombre</dc:title>
<dc:creator>I Funketti Allucinogeni</dc:creator>
<dc:subject class="BT">Effort</dc:subject>
<dc:subject class="NT">Music</dc:subject>
<dc:subject class="NT">Video</dc:subject>
<dc:abstract>This is a video of a song from the funk band called I Funketti Allucinogeni, edited with the supporters of the band from all over Italy during the Covid-19 pandemy.
</dc:abstract>
<dc:description>Ci siamo ritrovati da un giorno all’altro con tutte le date annullate. 
		Abbiamo pensato ingenuamente, non per superficialità ma solo per positività, che quello che ci stava circondando poteva essere solo un momento. Credevamo che si sarebbe poi sistemato tutto da quell’esatto momento all’altro. Ma giorno dopo giorno, abbiamo preso consapevolezza del fatto che la realtà e il suo significato erano completamente distaccati da quell’incertezza resa certezza del “è solo un momento”. 
		Per giorni e ancora ora,  ci è stato tolto tutto ciò che ci rende vivi: la musica. 
		E soprattutto il rapporto che abbiamo con essa. Dal soundcheck fino al ritorno a casa, col sudore e l’emozione che poi, dopo anni, è sempre la stessa. Ma ciò che ci mancava di più e ci tormentava ancora di più era il distacco, il piattume, l’apatia, la distanza con chi ci conosce, ha imparato a conoscerci e di conseguenza a sostenerci e a valorizzarci: il nostro pubblico. Abbiamo così pensato di realizzare il video di una canzone che trovate nel nostro primo EP omonimo, che è appunto è “OMBRE”, coinvolgendo proprio loro. 
		Quel piattume si è un po’ attenutato nel vedere i loro volti felici, cantare e ballare. E vederli insieme, uno dietro l’altro ci ha onestamente molto emozionati. 
		Perché è vero “Siamo solo ombre che si muovono nel buio”, ma durante il montaggio di quel video un po’ di luce è filtrata. 
</dc:description>
		<dc:description>From one day to the next, all our live concerts were cancelled. We thought, naively – not superficially but we wanted to stay positive – that what we were living could be just a moment. We believed that everything could go well, someway. But day by day, we realized that reality and its meaning were detached from our belief that “this will be just a moment”. For many days more and still now, they took away from us the only thing that keep us alive: music. 
		Above all our relationship with music. From soundcheck until coming back home, with the sweat and the emotion that, even after years, is still the same. What we missed most and what troubled us was detachment, apathy, distance between people who learnt to know us and, as a consequence, support us and enhance us: our fans. So we thought to realize the video of a song that is in our first EP that has the same name, “Ombre”, involving our supporters. 
		That apathy suddenly changed, seeing them happy to sing and dance. Seeing them together, made us happy and touched. 
		Because it’s true, “we’re only shadows that move in dark”, but during the editing of that video a little bit of light came along.
</dc:description>
<dc:publisher>IMOW - In My Own Words</dc:publisher>
<dc:publisher>GitHub</dc:publisher>
<dc:date xsi:type="dcterms:W3CDTF">27-03-2020</dc:date>
<dc:type>Video</dc:type>
<dc:format>mp4</dc:format>
<dc:source>User Provided</dc:source>
<dc:language>It</dc:language>
<dc:language>En</dc:language>
<dcterms:isPartOf>Effort</dcterms:isPartOf>
<dc:rights>Every right issues about the website and its content are specified in the Privacy Policy dedicated page that you can consult here: https://imowvirtualmuseum.github.io/GDPR_IMOW.pdf</dc:rights>
<dcterms:rightsholder>Every right issues about the website and its content are specified in the Privacy Policy dedicated page that you can consult here: https://imowvirtualmuseum.github.io/GDPR_IMOW.pdf</dcterms:rightsholder>

</metadata>