<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<metadata
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/">
<dc:title>Poor connection, stronger love</dc:title>
<dc:creator>Alessia Maniscalco</dc:creator>
<dc:subject class="BT">Love</dc:subject>
<dc:subject class="NT">Distance</dc:subject>
<dc:subject class="NT">Couple</dc:subject>
<dcterms:abstract> This is a photo taken by Alessia Maniscalco, while having a videocall with her boyfriend who was far during quarantine.</dcterms:abstract>
<dc:description>Sono 57 i giorni esatti che ci hanno tenuto distanti, condizione non tanto nuova per chi come noi ha sempre dovuto combattere con questa dura nemica che è la distanza, ora più che mai agguerrita.
Ma a modo nostro l’abbiamo sempre saputa fronteggiare, anche noi ora più che mai agguerriti. Telefonate, messaggi, fotomontaggi per poter vivere quei viaggi momentaneamente cancellati, film, bagni caldi e cene; condivisione di momenti che ci hanno riscoperto complici e che non sarebbero potuti diventare più speciali. 
Ed ecco una sdolcineria e una presa di coscienza: ho la conferma che di questo amore io non debba mai più dubitare, e che, cara distanza - tua alleata “poor connection” a parte - a noi non ci batti più.</dc:description>
<dc:description>There are 57 exact days that have kept us apart, a not so new condition for who like us have always had to fight with this tough enemy that is the distance, now more than ever fierce.
But in our own way we have always known how to face it, we too now more than ever fierce. Phone calls, messages, photo montages to be able to experience those temporarily canceled trips, films, hot baths and dinners; sharing moments that have rediscovered us accomplices and that could not have become more special. 
And here is a sweetness and an awareness: I have the confirmation that I must never doubt this love again, and that, dear distance - your ally "poor connection" aside - you cannot beat us anymore.</dc:description>
<dc:publisher>IMOW - In My Own Words</dc:publisher>
<dc:publisher>Github</dc:publisher>
<dc:date xsi:type="dcterms:W3CDTF">04-05-2020</dc:date>
<dc:type>Image</dc:type>
<dc:format>jpg</dc:format>
<dc:source>User Provided</dc:source>
<dc:language>It</dc:language>
<dc:language>En</dc:language>
<dcterms:isPartOf>Love</dcterms:isPartOf>
<dc:rights>Every right issues about the website and its content are specified in the Privacy Policy dedicated page that you can consult here</dc:rights>
<dcterms:rightsholder>Every right issues about the website and its content are specified in the Privacy Policy dedicated page that you can consult here</dcterms:rightsholder>

</metadata>