<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<metadata
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/">
<dc:title>The show must go on!</dc:title>
<dc:creator>Giulia Morini</dc:creator>
<dc:subject class="BT">Effort</dc:subject>
<dc:subject class="NT">Radio </dc:subject>
<dc:subject class="NT">Information</dc:subject>
<dcterms:abstract>This is an image provided by Giulia Morini that shows her in front of the headquarter of Radioimmaginaria. </dcterms:abstract>
<dc:description>Faccio parte di Radioimmaginaria da quando ho 14 anni, sono passati 10 anni e ogni giorno che vado in onda è sempre la stessa emozione. Anche durante il Covid non ci siamo fermati. Prima di tutto, tutte le redazioni che abbiamo in Italia e all’estero si sono organizzate per registrare la loro puntata settimanale a distanza. Noi più grandi invece abbiamo deciso di continuare a trasmettere, ogni giorno per un’ora per raccontare la vita degli adolescenti in quarantena. Parlare in radio con la mascherina è scomodissimo, andavo in iper ventilazione all’inizio, poi mi sono abituata. 
Ci si abitua a tutto, ma la cosa importante era trasmettere, fare informazione a nostro modo. E lo abbiamo fatto. 
Oggi c’è stata l’ultima puntata: 3 mesi, 64 puntate, 95 ospiti. Come sempre, è stato un onore poter raccontare e far sentire la nostra voce.
</dc:description>
<dc:description>I have been part of Radioimmaginaria since I was 14. 10 years have passed and every day that I am on air is always the same emotion. Even during Covid we didn't stop. First of all, all the editorial offices we have in Italy and abroad have organized themselves to record their weekly remote episode. Differently, because we are bigger than them, we decided to continue broadcasting, an hour for every day to tell the life of the teenagers in quarantine. Talking on the radio with the mask is very uncomfortable, I went into hyper ventilation at the beginning, then I got used to it. 
You get used to everything, but the important thing was to transmit, to make information in our way. And we did it. 
Today was the last episode: 3 months, 64 episodes, 95 guests. As always, it was an honor to be able to tell and make our voice heard.
</dc:description>
<dc:publisher>IMOW - In My Own Words</dc:publisher>
<dc:publisher>Github</dc:publisher>
<dc:date xsi:type="dcterms:W3CDTF">10-04-2020</dc:date>
<dc:type>Image</dc:type>
<dc:format>jpg</dc:format>
<dc:source>User Provided</dc:source>
<dc:language>It</dc:language>
<dc:language>En</dc:language>
<dcterms:isPartOf>Effort</dcterms:isPartOf>
<dc:rights>Every right issues about the website and its content are specified in the Privacy Policy dedicated page that you can consult here</dc:rights>
<dcterms:rightsholder>Every right issues about the website and its content are specified in the Privacy Policy dedicated page that you can consult here</dcterms:rightsholder>

</metadata>