<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<metadata
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/">
<dc:title>Soul SISTERS</dc:title>
<dc:creator>Francesca Cartanì</dc:creator>
<dc:subject class="BT">Love</dc:subject>
<dc:subject class="NT">Video </dc:subject>
<dc:subject class="NT">Sisters</dc:subject>
<dcterms:abstract>This is a video made by Francesca Cartanì showing her with her sister.</dcterms:abstract>
<dc:description>Questa quarantena per me è diventata il modo per vivere mia sorella come mai avevo fatto prima. Per tanto tempo l’ho sempre vista come una seconda mamma, spesso più severa, l’ho sempre guardata dal basso verso l’alto, un modello che speravo un giorno di raggiungere. 
L’ho scoperta, però, non solo sorella, ma complice e amica. Ci siamo ritrovate a guardare film insieme nel letto, cosa ahimè mai fatta, e come ha sempre fatto, si è presa cura di me dall’interno e dall’esterno. 
Ci siamo fatte compagnia in una distanza forzata dai nostri fidanzati. 
Ci siamo felicemente ri-scoperte, non avrei voluto nessun altro al mio fianco.
</dc:description>
<dc:description>This quarantine for me has become a way to live with my sister like I never did before. For a long time I have always seen her as a second mother, often more severe, I have always looked at her from the bottom up, a model that I hoped one day to reach.
However, I discovered her not only sister, but an accomplice and friend. We found ourselves watching movies together in bed, a thing unfortunately we never did, and as she always has, she has taken care of me from the inside and from the outside.
We kept ourself company in a forced distance from our boyfriends.
We happily re-discovered each other, I wouldn't have wanted anyone else by my side.
</dc:description>
<dc:publisher>IMOW - In My Own Words</dc:publisher>
<dc:publisher>Github</dc:publisher>
<dc:date>unknown</dc:date>
<dc:type>Video</dc:type>
<dc:format>mp4</dc:format>
<dc:source>User Provided</dc:source>
<dc:language>It</dc:language>
<dc:language>En</dc:language>
<dcterms:isPartOf>Love</dcterms:isPartOf>
<dc:rights>Every right issues about the website and its content are specified in the Privacy Policy dedicated page that you can consult here: https://imowvirtualmuseum.github.io/GDPR_IMOW.pdf</dc:rights>
<dcterms:rightsholder>Every right issues about the website and its content are specified in the Privacy Policy dedicated page that you can consult here: https://imowvirtualmuseum.github.io/GDPR_IMOW.pdf</dcterms:rightsholder>

</metadata>