<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<metadata
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/">
<dc:title>Spesa solidale</dc:title>
<dc:creator>Mikaela Arteaga</dc:creator>
<dc:subject class="BT">Solidarity</dc:subject>
<dc:subject class="NT">Volunteering</dc:subject>
<dcterms:abstract>In this story, Mikaela Arteaga tells her experience of volunteering during quarantine.</dcterms:abstract>
<dc:description>
All’inizio non ci volevo credere che si parlasse di pandemia globale e che le nostre vite dovessero cambiare. la paura che c’era nella gente si sentiva nonostante nelle  strade c’era un silenzio assordante. Ero consapevole che per alcune persone non sarebbe  stato facile affrontare questo problema, per questo motivo ho deciso di aderire al servizio volontariato organizzato dal comune e parrocchia di Fiorenzuola D’arda.  Mi occupavo nel portare la spesa di alimenti e/o farmaci a casa delle persone anziane e per chi fosse in quarantena. 
Mi ha fatto piacere vedere questi gesti di solidarietà verso il prossimo e che io ne potessi fare parte, vedere negli occhi degli assistiti la loro gratitudine e averli fatti sentire che non erano da soli.
</dc:description>
<dc:description>At first, I didn’t want to believe that it was a global pandemy for real and that our lives had to change. You could perceive fear of people, despite the silence among the streets. I was conscious that for many people it wouldn’t have been simple to face this problem, so I decided to join volunteering service organized by the municipality and the church of Fiorenzuola D’Arda. I handled with bringing groceries or medicines to older people’s house and to the ones in quarantine. I was glad to see these actions of solidarity to the neighbors and the fact that I was part of that, seeing in the eyes of those people gratitude. I was glad to let them feel they were not alone.
</dc:description>
<dc:publisher>IMOW - In My Own Words</dc:publisher>
<dc:publisher>Github</dc:publisher>
<dc:date xsi:type="dcterms:W3CDTF">17-03-2020</dc:date>
<dc:type>Image</dc:type>
<dc:format>jpg</dc:format>
<dc:source>User Provided</dc:source>
<dc:language>It</dc:language>
<dc:language>En</dc:language>
<dcterms:isPartOf>Solidarity</dcterms:isPartOf>
<dc:rights>Every right issues about the website and its content are specified in the Privacy Policy dedicated page that you can consult here</dc:rights>
<dcterms:rightsholder>Every right issues about the website and its content are specified in the Privacy Policy dedicated page that you can consult here</dcterms:rightsholder>

</metadata>